《外星居民》前情提要...
哈利不能和那只鸟约会。
他应该拯救地球。
传送门已经修好了吧？
我们要搬到她的家乡星球。
有些人发现皮肤有碎屑
外星人用作追踪设备。
副官，我们在这里得到了什么？
有人在公交车站附近发现了它。
我会仔细检查一下，看看它属于谁。
你永远不会知道像希瑟和我这样的爱情。
我们互不保守秘密
就像人类一样。
你要帮助我们获取哈利的外星人 DNA。
你将离开这个星球，
你再也见不到他了。
这他妈到底是什么？
发现小灰人的计划后
改变地球的大气层，
我已经制定了自己的计划。
我正在制造一枚可以摧毁小灰人飞船的炸弹。
然后是他们愚蠢而美丽的混血儿
将被困在这里并且必须找到工作
作为私人教练和场外记者。
呃哦。
有问题。
我的血糖低得危险。
一旦将军拿到炸弹，她就可以完成任务，
我可以开始我的新生活了——
离开地球并消费
我和希瑟一起度过余生。
早上好，我美丽的天堂鸟。
毫米。
我可以给你做一顿美味的早餐吗？
我有一碗蠕虫和昆虫。
或者说还有一个
冰箱里的水生无脊椎动物。
哦，没关系。
我——我其实并不饿。
好的。
好吧，我可以，呃，咀嚼它。
将其重新送回嘴中。
这真的很甜蜜，但是不，谢谢。
我想我——我真的睡得不好。
你的人床不如鸟巢舒服
你让我在旅馆里。
那我今天就给你造一个新窝。
我会进城，收集树枝
还有绳子和一些头发。
不，哈利，你已经做得太多了。
我想为你做点什么。
侧翼工作？
更好的东西。
首先，我需要你改变。
你的鳃肯定需要清洁。
还有更多的来源。
你喜欢这个？
是的，我愿意。
哦，找到一个人真是太好了
你可以做你自己。
把一切都放在开放的地方。
没有秘密。
嗯嗯。
是的。
亲爱的，你的头在晃动。
哦。
你有什么心事吗？
诡异的。
呃，不。
什么都没有。
绝对没有什么可隐瞒的。
这是肯定的。
你可以再努力一点。
我喜欢这种痛苦。
哦。
我们可能需要一个安全词。
- 嘿。- 嘿。
你在这儿做什么？
我工作到很晚，所以...
回家路上我累了，就停了下来。
我的家不在你回家的路上。
你抓住了我。
我只是过来确认一下你还好吗
你就睡在这里吗？
我是说，你怎么上厕所的？
等待。
是关于你那天晚上说的那些外星人的事情吗？
外星人？
太疯狂了。
不，我只是——看看你。
如果这能让外星人远离，那就太好了。
我没有被外星人绑架
所以你需要在凯特出来之前回家
并开始提问。- 美好的。
嘿，你能帮我扔掉我的水瓶吗？
你尿在里面了吗？
你知道我做到了。
相当饱满。闻起来像尿尿。
你会把它扔掉吗，是还是不是？
- 不。 - 试一试。
里面全是尿。
真的吗？
这只是撒尿。
爱是的。
呵呵。迷人的。
你在这。
告诉我你没有再住一晚
守卫本和凯特的房子。
是的，但他抓住了我，
所以不能再这样做了。
今晚我得带双筒望远镜
把车停在街上，从那里观看。
这里有什么计划？
假设您目睹了一次绑架​​。
你究竟要如何阻止它？
棒球棒。
我在网上看过格雷斯的照片。
他们的脖子很长，他们的头
就在我的好球区。
不是抱怨，但这会杀了杰伊吗
偶尔洗一次盘子？
这听起来像是在抱怨。
我知道。
她是你的女儿，事实上
解释了她为什么不打扫卫生。
但她的东西却无处不在。
折叠沙发，始终打开。
哦，我的覆盆子酸奶又没了。
大惊喜。
- 你昨天已经完成了。- 是的。
因为我知道如果我不这样做，杰伊就会吃掉它。
美好的。
我会给你买更多的酸奶和干净的。
快乐的？
不。
杰应该这么做。
听着，我和杰伊现在关系真的很好，
我不想惹事生非。
此外，我们还有更大的事情要担心，
比如如何阻止哈利和希瑟一起离开。
杰似乎是我们当中最不重要的——
汤，家人？
仅供参考，你没奶了。
杰伊是我们当中最不重要的——你是说？
请别打扰我。
没有什么比一次好的鳃挖掘更好的了
让你再次焕然一新。
我能做什么来感谢你呢？
你不需要感谢我。
我不值得。
你值得拥有一切。
这就是为什么我要完成这个炸弹，
这样我们就可以离开，并且永远不会回头。
我迫不及待地想看看你的星球。
你的朋友会接受吗
你正在和一个没有翅膀的外星人约会？
我们先不谈未来。
让我们来谈谈现在吧
因为它太特别了。
你知道，我想这就是为什么他们称之为现在，
因为这是一份礼物。
这让我想起，我给你写了一首新诗。
你做到了吗？
我喜欢你的诗。
但别读给我听。
就停在那里，不要读它，
因为我要把这个拿出来
如果我不马上回来
那只是因为我跑出去买烟了。
但你甚至不抽烟。
我喜欢你尝试新事物。
这应该就是真爱的样子吧。
当你的爱人离开时，
你感觉你再也见不到他们了。
还有她的轮胎从我的车道上剥落的声音，
我看得出来她急着回到我身边。
给你，黛布拉。
早上好，警长。
嘿，副官。
嘿，你有没有过这样的感觉——
就像你被跟踪一样？
现在就想到了。
昨晚，我感觉有人跟踪我。
所以今天早上我改变了路线
但我认为约瑟夫那个混蛋还在跟踪我。
你知道这意味着什么，不是吗？
我们的调查进展顺利。
我们的调查？不。
我告诉过你，当我介入时，人们就会受伤。
我受够了。
什么？
我以为你只是需要时间
我不需要时间。
我需要距离。
花点时间可以帮助你更清楚地看待事情，副官。
嘿，你知道，克莱图斯曾经在我床上撒尿过，对吧？
现在，我很生气，但我摆脱了他吗？
不。
我花了一些时间反思
并找到正确的行动。
然后我就去他的小床上撒尿了
我对他说：“现在，你觉得怎么样？”
他就是这样学习的。
他们在你身上撒尿，你也在他们身上撒尿。
我不会去碰他的鼻子。
那就太残忍了。
不比我听这个故事更残酷。
嘿。
呃，我需要和你们谈谈一些事情。
我有一些抱怨
关于治安部门。
我告诉过你这是一个糟糕的主意
设立该意见箱。
是的，我是从您在建议箱中添加的注释中得知的
告诉我把意见箱拿下来。
似乎某些成分
对纳税人的钱不满意
浪费时间去调查与外星人有关的事情。
纳税人不应该有发言权
他们的税款如何花掉。
这就是无政府状态。
嗯，有些人称之为民主。
确切地。
这是一个自由的国家。
人们如果愿意的话可以寻找外星人
或在森林中寻找仙女，
即使他们只找到一只小青蛙
住在旧猎枪壳里。
你说有些人提出投诉。
我想知道是谁。
我不敢说。
嗨，警长。
娜娜。
谢谢市长给我们的简短谈话。
哦，来吧，丽芙。
你如何期望人们认真对待你
你的裤子上有那个折痕吗？
啊。
她是对的。
我确实有一个折痕。
她怎么看到的？
警长，我想在我的办公室见你。
毫米。
好吧，警长，请坐。
我要求在我的办公室见你。
不，你说
你想在你的办公室见我。
我不怪你。
天哪，我是一尊男子气概的雕像。
如果我在你的办公室，你可能会走进去
每天早上说：“该死，现在，这就是我想成为的人。”
如果你是我办公室里的一尊雕像
我会把我的夹克挂在你身上。
我希望你这么做，因为我会被创造
金属的，我会很冷。
看？
即使作为一个雕像人，我仍然得到我想要的。
好的，事情是这样的。
有人在镇上看到你和丽芙
穿着便衣窥探，调查某事。
更不用说，你知道，你实际上是如何求我的
寻找新的副手，但现在他走了
你还没有取代他吗？
到底是怎么回事？
你为什么这么神秘？
你为什么这么好奇？
因为我有权利知道。
这是我的城镇。- 哦真的吗？
你显然不知道城镇是如何运作的。
你看过西部片吗？
是治安官说，“你现在在我的镇上，”
不是市长。
你开的车上写着“市长”吗？
是的，我愿意。
- 你做？- 是的。
有时候脏了的时候
麦克斯在窗口写下“市长”，
那就是市长，
如“愿你...
“镇上，如果遇到麻烦，
我将成为解决这个问题的人。”
你的车门上可能有“警长”这个词，
但印着“霍桑”这个名字
在这个小镇的灵魂上。
正确的。就像那条毒溪。
忘记小溪吧。
那就是改名了
我不知道你为什么会这样。
你知道，我们曾经就像伙伴一样。
我们从来都不是合作伙伴。
我们在分裂的政府形式下运作，
像马达加斯加或东帝汶，
两位领导人分享不同的权力，好吗？
现在，如果你不介意的话，我还有工作要做。
人类通过建立彼此的联系而蓬勃发展。
但当这种联系被打破时
这让他们感觉不受束缚。
他们不喜欢那样。
这就是我开始的感受。
希瑟已经离开两个小时了
我能想到的就是，如果她受伤了怎么办？
如果她被拔毛塞进枕头怎么办
还是舒适轻便的夹克？
你好。
哦。
谢谢。
“哈利，如果你正在读这篇文章，
“那么你就认识了我的朋友阿洛。
我要离开这个没有你的星球。”
不。
“别找我。
“请给阿洛一些麦片，
如果你不介意的话。”
这不可能。
♪ 一是最孤独的数字 ♪
“我怎么知道这真的是你？
另外，我的麦片也没有了。”
♪ 两个人和一个人一样糟糕
♪ 这是最孤独的数字
好的，就这样吧。
♪ 从第一名开始
哦，这么快。
你回来了。
♪ 不，才是最悲伤的经历 ♪
“是的，确实是我。
“还有谁会用鸽子寄纸条呢？
PS，阿洛也喜欢美味的饼干。”
“为什么？
“发生了什么事？
“而且，阿洛不会吃我的饼干。
它们是胡椒类的。”
♪ 一是最孤独的数字 ♪
♪ 一个人是最孤独的
♪ 你会做的数字
希瑟。
我们不能一直做笔记。
这对阿洛不公平。
他快累坏了
我的爱人，你回来了。
不，哈利，一切都结束了。
什么？
但为什么？
因为我不爱你。
我从没干过。
不。
我不相信你。啊! 噢。
为什么？噢。
我想我的心脏正在停止跳动。
它不是。
宇宙中唯一的东西就是心
即使它们损坏后也能正常工作。
这是令人心烦意乱的事情。
你怎么知道？
是不是因为你的心也碎了？
不。
我的心还好
感觉很棒。
好吧，你不能带走我们的爱。
这不只是你的。
这也是我的。
抱歉，我必须要走了。
不，等等，我——
我有一首诗要读给你听。
你必须听。
标题是《永远在一起》。
“孩子，我简直无法停止微笑。”
- 不，我不能这样做。
我不能做到这一点。
好的 -
好什么？
“好的”？
“天哪，我爱你。”
“还好我是在开玩笑。”
哈哈哈哈！
啊？
“再见。”
为什么？
抓住你了，混蛋。
等等，你不是约瑟夫。
我——我是特洛伊。
特洛伊？
哇哦。
你是莉娜的儿子吗？
我只是好奇而已。
我想见见我妈妈正在约会的那个人。
来吧，儿子。
你不能跟随周围的人
在黑暗中，好吗？
这很危险。你可以放松一下。
我们没有约会。我们只是同事。
她不谈论她的其他同事
她谈论你的方式。
她谈论我？
我无意中听到她告诉我娜雅阿姨
你不喜欢她付钱买东西吗？
我不明白。
她付钱有什么问题吗？
听着，我很感激你在这里
为了保护你妈妈，好吗？
但这是成年人的事情。
你不会明白的。情况很复杂。
不，这不对。
从现在开始，你离她远点。
好吧，好吧，她已经远离我了。
她为什么不呢？
你让她哭了。
你是一个什么样的人？
哈利？
我收到一条短信说你想死
接下来是一个骷髅表情符号，
然后是绞索，然后是枪。
是的。然后是一把刀和一个棺材。
然后出于某种原因，一座教堂？
那是个错误。
本来应该是一把剑。
这是怎么回事？
希瑟离开了我。
是的。
是的，她做到了。
那太糟糕了。
她走了。
结束了。
现在我的生命结束了。
哦，我很抱歉，哈利。
不撒谎。
你很高兴。
红发的人努力忍住不笑。
看来你现在已经知道我的名字了。
好的。
听着，我们确实试图拆散你们，
但它不起作用。- 正确的。
所以也许只有你是这样的。
这有帮助吗？
我...
你错了。
希瑟爱我。
我爱过她。
我不知道发生了什么事。
有时没有解释。
哦。
嘿。
你只需要把你的心思从她身上移开，你知道的。
保持忙碌。
在这里专注于您的小项目。
哈，那是什么？
某种外星喂鸟器？
- 这是一颗炸弹。- 你说的是炸弹。
那现在是什么？
我建造它是为了一般人使用
我和希瑟离开后，在灰人家。
好的。
嗯，拯救地球，这是我们活着的目标。
我不关心地球。
这个地方很糟糕。
我讨厌这里！
呃！
嘿，格雷斯！
快来占领这个地球吧！
我不想要它！
你可以拥有它！
嘿，拿走这个愚蠢的植物！
我不想要它！
你可以拥有它！
拿走这把愚蠢的椅子！
啊？
我不在乎了！
- 好的。- 带我去！
我想死！
好的，请回到这里好吗？
吃点东西也许你会感觉好点。
我们给你买了一份披萨。
我不在乎你的披萨。
我恨地球，我也恨你。
哇！
我不是这样教你做人的。
阿斯塔努力工作才买了披萨，年轻人。
你会把你的屁股拿出来吃它。
我不在乎，我讨厌你！
我更恨你！
你知道，这是我一生中第一次，
我觉得我具备了当母亲的条件。
我终于见到了莉娜的儿子。
他一直在跟踪我。
他想看看他妈妈在和谁约会。
想谈谈吗？
现在。
没什么可谈的。
她说我们是同事，但后来我发现
她因分手而哭泣。
看来你想谈谈它。
不，不。
这是我们的安静时光。
安静的时光。
你知道，也许这就是我的命运
你知道，独自一人。
好的。
让我们来谈谈它。
她的孩子是对的。
什么样的男人有特别的人
然后就——就将她推开？
那种失去母亲的男人
当他年轻时，由父亲抚养长大。
你对这些男子气概的观念很着迷。
所以对自己放轻松一点。
这不是你的错。
现在我们可以钓鱼了吗？
你是那个想说话的人。
他是认真的想要离开。
这东西有所有的说明
关于如何处理这枚炸弹。
好吧，任何有成效的事情都会暂时搁置。
他只是问男人是否可以成为修女。
也许是最好的。
我不知道现在是否要他处理炸弹。
我厌倦了扮演这个外星孩子的父母。
自己在家做就够了。
是的。
什么？
没有什么。
你只是没有真正在家做这件事。
我告诉过你，杰伊和我处境很好。
我不想破坏它。- 正确的。
你害怕惹恼和我们住在一起的青少年
还吃了我的酸奶，所以现在我没有酸奶了。
我不害怕。
是的，你是。
你害怕你会失去她。
而你却在帮助和教唆她。
协助和教唆？
什么，现在喝酸奶是重罪吗？
不，这只是，你想成为
她的朋友而不仅仅是一个负责任的成年人。
如果我这么不负责任，你为什么跑来找我？
每次你遇到麻烦的时候？
因为你让我，这可能是
老实说，这整个问题是如何开始的。
哦，哦，好的。
所以我毁了你，因为我在你身边
你什么时候需要我？
不，只要你愿意，你就在我身边
当它让你自我感觉更好时
就像哈利说的。
谢谢。
告诉我一次我不在你身边。
哦，我不知道，也许当你让我发疯的时候
对我保守一个改变生活的秘密
一年半了？
哦真的吗？又是这个？
我应该做什么，
告诉你新医生是外星人？
是的！
我应该是你最好的朋友
但你不能与我分享。
为什么？
我不打算讨论这个。
好吧，我们就在其中。
让我们把它放下吧，拜托。
我不想丢掉它。
我想知道为什么。
因为你是一门松散的大炮，
我不知道我是否可以信任你。
这就是你想听的吗？
你太冲动了
我只知道你会告诉别人。
那是胡说。
你不想告诉我因为哈利
降落到地球对你来说是天赐之物。
只有你。
你在自家门口发现的秘密小宝贝，
另一件是为你的贫困者动物园准备的。
你告诉本他被绑架了
当我告诉你不要这样做时。
无论如何你还是这么做了，因为你不听
因为一切都是你自己创造的。
我不。
我怎样才能让一切都围绕我自己？
告诉我。我想知道。
在这种否认中，有很多“我的”和“我的”。
我告诉本因为真正的朋友
不要互相保守巨大的秘密。
你告诉本是因为你感到内疚
所以你创造了关于你的一切。
好的。美好的。
我创造了关于我的一切。
但你创造了关于你的一切
说这与你无关，因为你是烈士
我宁愿当烈士，也不愿当一门松散的大炮。
嗯，这正是烈士会说的话。
- 松动的大​​炮。- 烈士。
假装我不在这里。
你为什么在这？
我是来看看你过得怎么样。
你穿好衣服了吗？
脱衣服？
或者现在就是这样？
你会这样问女人吗？
你的朋友阿斯塔联系了我。
说你一团糟，无法工作。
现在我不知道第一件事
关于如何安慰患相思病的外星人，
但我听说了你的鸡女友
或者无论她是什么。
所以...
这他妈到底是什么？
那家伙说她的名字叫帕特里夏。
我想也许她可以帮助你
克服你的女朋友。
没有判断力。
每个人都有自己的事情。
我很生气你认为
你可以取代我一生的挚爱
只是一些随机的鸟。
没有冒犯的意思。
这与你无关。
你非常迷人。
做任何你需要的事情。
完成那个炸弹。
并且不要坠入爱河。
她是租来的。
别担心，我们什么都不用做。
我们可以谈谈。
尽管我自己从未遇到过不明飞行物
我来这里是为了支持我的女儿
因为我爱她。
我也爱你，妈妈。
哦，宝贝。
好的。
谢谢你的分享，多萝西。
所以这就是所有疯子聚集的地方。
我预计墙上会有更多的填充物。
- 你好。- 你来了。
是的。我当时就在附近，
所以我想我也可以。
你是新来的。
您想向我们介绍一下您自己
你为什么在这里？
哦，我？不。
嗯，我……我不是来参加的。
我只是来看看。
我们这里没有很多观察者。
嗯，我——我什么也没经历过。
我的意思是，我——
我一直在窗外看到这只猫头鹰。
但这没什么大不了的。
我的意思是，这是科罗拉多州，对吗？
有猫头鹰。
实际上有14个品种。
我--我在网上查了一下。
所以，你知道，不，我——
我想我很好。
除了，嗯，我不是——我不好。
我是...
我曾经很喜欢我住的地方。
但现在——我的意思是，我爱我们的——我们的家，但是……
但我在那里感觉不安全。
我是说，我——我什至——
我什至试图说服我丈夫卖掉我们的房子。
但我认为它比那更大。
就像，我想我在任何地方都不安全。
我只是觉得我快要疯了。
哦，我可以在这里使用这个词吗？
你没有疯。
我也有过类似的经历。
起初，猫头鹰似乎并不奇怪，
但随后这种事就不断发生。
我什至把我们的房子挂牌出售。
然后有一天，我在洗澡时，
我发现膝盖后面有一个小肿块
我从来没有注意到。
所以我做了一些研究，然后我意识到
这可能是他们植入我体内的芯片
以及世界各地的人们
都有过类似的经历。
你还好吗？
我不知道。
他知道你在提取他的 DNA吗？
不。
不过我感觉很糟糕。
我爱他。
噢，真甜。
你爱你的侄女吗？
我的膝盖？
你要打断我的膝盖吗？
侄女。
你的侄女，你姐姐的孩子。- 好的。
好吧，你可以直接说我姐姐。
我也爱她。
哦，快点。
侄女和膝盖，截然不同。
为何如此？
侄女是一个小女孩或法国的一座城市。
我不摔断膝盖。
我就在现场
看着阿斯塔的男朋友和哈利的女朋友
有一个约会。
她们两个听起来都像我姐姐的女儿。
你有一个叫膝盖的侄女吗？
是的。她是我的侄女。
我们怎么输给你们了？
轮班报告供您签署。
一切都好吗，副官？
你脸上挂着悲伤的表情。
真的吗？
我有一张悲伤的脸吗？
我会给你一个提示。
在这里，把这支铅笔放进嘴里。
侧身。
就这样吧。
你感觉到你的微笑肌肉在伸展吗？
看吧，当你悲伤的时候，你欺骗了你的身体
认为你是幸福的，然后你就会感到幸福。
多久时间？
呃，七分钟。
当然，我是专业人士，所以我用了三分钟就完成了
使用同一支铅笔。
告诉我，副官，是什么让你如此沮丧？
我今天参加了一场会议。
这个女人，琳达，带来了她的妈妈。
她只是来支持她的女儿。
我从来没有得到过这样的支持，
我可能永远不会。
毫米。
你知道吗？请坐，副官。
我——我想告诉你一个关于这个人的故事。
- 这个人是你吗？
呃，没关系。
不管怎样，有这么一个帅哥
味道真好，对吧？
他在青少年时期就失去了母亲。
现在，他的父亲——刘易斯？
我可以给你讲完这个人的故事吗？
- 是的。- 好吧，所以他的——他的父亲，
他可能推动了他的男子气概观念
对这个家伙有点太严厉了吧？
也许如果这个人能直面他的问题
早些年，他不会
让他的自我战胜他
还推开了一个完美的女人。
这个女人是莉娜·托雷斯吗？
我们就叫她米娜·弗洛雷斯吧。
好吧，听着，我的观点是，
我们是由养育我们的人塑造的。
而且你周围的人也不太支持你。
事实上，他们主动压制你。
现在你是我认识的最坚强的人
除非你在帕蒂奶奶身边。
你需要勇敢地面对她。
我不能。
她很刻薄，而且给人一种看似强大的感觉。
好吧，如果我告诉你我认识一个愿意和你一起去的人呢？
并给予你从未有过的所有支持？
这家伙是你吗？
哈！
你终于想通了。
♪ 休假了
♪ 你习惯的方式 ♪
♪ 新的一天是寻找新的自己的方法 ♪
♪ 我真的不确定你认为我注册的目的是什么 ♪
♪ 跳过加演吧，我已经受够了 ♪
♪ 我不需要更多
有时间我会给你上一课。
一直想办法联系到你
但我看到你很忙。
兄弟，雪下得真棒。
你应该和我们一起去的。
是啊，随心所欲地下班一定很好。
太冲动了你知道吗？
好的。
那又怎样，你现在对我滑雪有意见吗？
没有。
哈利在哪儿？
我不知道。
上次我见到他的时候，我和你在一起。
嗯，我去了小屋，
但他不在那儿。
我只找到一只巨鸟
谁不是希瑟。
他绝对有一个类型。
好的。你为什么要找他？
朱迪看到约瑟夫正在和希瑟说话。
什么？在哪里？
我在现场，看着——
忽略——她开了滤镜。
我听不到他们在说什么。
我勒个去？
这只鸟是小灰人的间谍吗？
我们必须找到哈利并告诉他。
我知道他沮丧时会去哪里。
谢谢你带我们上山，史蒂夫。
是的，没问题。
无论如何，我必须飞越南峰。
我想你和我必须在周六澄清这一点。
凉爽的。
雪崩控制很重要，对吗？
嘿，你担心吗
我是某种松​​散的大炮
我会和你一起去那里
然后就把你推下山？
不。
啊。
所以你不会认为我是一个松散的大炮。
所以你相信我。有趣的。
史蒂夫，你不觉得这对某人来说很奇怪吗
骂你花时间陪你女儿？
我没有女儿。
是的，但你不认为，
在你经历了一切之后
你已经赢得了和她一起出去玩的权利了吗？
你知道，要无忧无虑一点。
嘿，史蒂夫，你想粉刷一下浴室吗
紫红色和呕吐物的组合
让沐浴时间变得愉快？
史蒂夫，你能买一张小咖啡桌吗
这么小，连咖啡桌上的书都放不下？
我们没有咖啡桌上的书。
因为茶几太小了。
我的天啊。我 -
我敲不了门。
我太紧张了。
当我来到这里时，这种情况总是发生。
没关系。
你刚刚给自己带来了一点“害羞”的情况。
我会全程陪着你。
来吧，握紧拳头。
噢。
我认为他们流了一点血。
丽芙。警长。
这是怎么回事？
我想和你谈谈一些事情。
你不能只给我发一封电子邮件吗？
我为什么费心去学习互联网
如果你要亲自出现？
好吧，进来吧。
擦脚。
这不是一家廉价旅馆。
嗯，那是什么？
你知道你所说的一切
关于我的头发和脸
以及关于我的几乎一切？
是的。
这——感觉有点卑鄙。
但这可能不是你的错
因为我知道你们这一代人过得很艰难
伴随着战争和一切，嗯，
我知道你出生在曾祖父的干草车里。
哦，你想道歉。
好的。
我原谅你。
是这样吗？- 是的。
呃，不在场，呃——
难道没有别的事吗？
Ay-yi-yi.
好吧，我承认，
我偷了你的芥末蛋食谱，娜娜，
但这只是因为我欣赏你的厨艺
我很欣赏你。
我想成为像你一样的人
但后来你却对着全家人对我说了垃圾话。
现在你已经说了所有那些可怕的话
镇上的报纸上有关于我的事。
为什么要这么做？
我只是说了实话。
我经常做。
哦真的吗？
嗯，我也可以说点真话。
哦。
祖母应该是和蔼可亲的
闻起来像饼干，
但你却残忍恶毒，浑身散发着醋味。
不是那种用来蘸面包的甜香脂，
但是英国的炸薯条醋。
好吧，你有点偏离轨道了。
小女孩就应该幸福
去看他们的奶奶，但我总是害怕，
因为你让我感到自己的渺小和无价值
我仍然有这种感觉，但我不会再这样了
因为你是个小人，
而你就是那个一文不值的人。
将其拨回一点。
你是一个古老的、愤怒的——--------，
你可以拿走那个------芥末蛋----
并制作一些------食谱和-----
把它塞满你的---------！
好的没问题。这就够了。
不不不。我才刚刚开始。
她在假装。
加里说她会没事的。
这只是一次轻微的心脏病发作。
我是说，当我们出现时她脸色苍白
所以她可能已经处于心脏病发作的前兆了。
谢谢。
另外，我告诉加勒特她有妄想症。
所以没有人会相信她的故事。
我喜欢住在小镇。
是的。你拿到你的食谱了吗？
是的。
谢谢你撬开锁。
我们走吧。我们从来没有来过这里。
决不。
♪ 如果可以的话，宝贝，你在哪里 ♪
♪ 那我就知道了
♪ 宝贝，你知道什么
告诉过你他会在这里。
♪ 宝贝，就在你所在的地方 ♪
你们两个在这里做什么？
希瑟正在和约瑟夫一起工作。
她走了已经够糟糕的了。
现在你正在散布关于那个女人的谎言
我曾经爱过，但现在希望它死了。
这不是谎言，哈利。
朱迪看到希瑟给了约瑟夫一个垃圾袋。
你知道为什么吗？
这是一个蓝色的垃圾袋吗？
是的。
她清理了我的鳃并将粘稠物放在那里。
你知道她为什么想把这些东西给约瑟夫吗？
我的DNA。
他们想克隆我。
他们有我的外星人球。
他们正试图操纵它。
但我把它给了外星人追踪者的儿子罗伯特。
如果灰人队绑架了他，那么他们就有球权。
你们这里有接待处吗？如何？
这很容易。
您只需进入设置即可。
它会提示你。
“你想驾驭这座山吗？
“用作您自己的个人手机信号塔
因为你是一个聪明的外星人？”
你只需按“是”即可。
太有趣了。
你好，儿子。
这是哈利，你的新父亲。
呃，不是死人。
呃，你好吗？
你还在地球吗？
是的。
我和伙计们在麦芽店。
灰队拥有球权。
他们要用它做什么？
我们的技术全部基于氢。
它帮助我们操纵水。
但如果小灰人能做到，他们就能加快速度
他们对黄石洞穴的计划。
等等，所以他们现在随时都可以毁灭地球？
更差。
我一生的挚爱并没有离开我。
她背叛了我。
爱就像生命线
将宇航员拴在他的船上。
如果这条线被切断，你就迷路了。
这就是我的感受，与唯一的爱隔绝了
我永远都会知道。
当我们所相信和信任的事物失去联系时，
就像我们呼吸的空气消失了一样。
达西，我们谈谈好吗？
♪ 你的影像
♪ 这是持续的折磨
♪ 但我不知道还能做什么 ♪
然后，保持联系就成为生存问题。
♪ 只有那些黑色的大秃鹰才会问我过得怎么样 ♪
♪ 你不骄傲吗
♪ 哦，哦，嘿
♪ 她是一只蓝鸟
♪ 现在我们分开了
♪ 我希望有一只大狼 ♪
♪ 这会撕裂她死去的心 ♪
♪ 没有爱
♪ 我简直不敢相信
♪ 但这是真的
♪ 这是真的
♪ 我很生气
♪ 我生气了，我生气了，我生气了，我生气了 ♪
我勒个去？
♪ 专为您打造，看起来非常漂亮 ♪
那么是什么让您来到这片树林呢？
♪ 永远都是这样 ♪
我是来杀我父亲的
♪ 哦，记住你发现的每一天 ♪
♪ 你心里有一点小麻烦 ♪
♪ 你会在附近找到我，因为我永远都在 ♪
♪ 只为你，你也为我 ♪
Previously on
"Resident Alien"...
Harry can't date that bird.
He should be saving the Earth.
The portal is fixed, yeah?
We are moving
to her home planet.
Some people find
chips in their skin
that aliens use
as a tracking device.
What do we got here, Deputy?
Someone found it
near the bus stop.
I'll go through it
and see who it belongs to.
You will never know
a love like Heather and I.
We do not keep secrets
from one another
like humans do.
You are gonna help us
get Harry's alien DNA.
You will leave the planet,
and you will never
see him again.
What the hell is that?
After discovering
the Greys' plan
to change
the Earth's atmosphere,
I have devised
a plan of my own.
I am building a bomb that can
destroy the Greys' spaceship.
And then their stupid,
beautiful hybrids
will be stuck here
and have to get jobs
as personal trainers
and sideline reporters.
Uh-oh.
Something is wrong.
My blood sugar is
dangerously low.
Once the general has the bomb,
she can finish the mission,
and I can embark
on my new one--
leaving the planet
and spending
the rest of my life
with Heather.
Good morning, my beautiful
bird of paradise.
Mm.
Can I make you
a nice breakfast, hmm?
I have a bowl
of worms and insects.
Or there is also still one
aquatic invertebrate
in the fridge.
Oh, that's OK.
I'm--I'm not really hungry.
OK.
Well, I could, uh, chew it up.
Regurgitate it
back in your mouth.
That's really sweet,
but no, thanks.
I think that I--
I didn't really sleep well.
Your human bed is not
as comfortable as the nest
you made me at the hotel.
Then I will make you
a new nest today.
I will go into town,
and I will gather twigs
and string and some hair.
No, Harry, you've already
done too much.
I want to do something for you.
A wing job?
Something even better.
First, I need you to change.
Your gills definitely
needed a cleaning.
There's more
where that came from.
You like this?
Yes, I do.
Oh, it is so nice
to find someone
you can be yourself with.
Just leave everything
out in the open.
No secrets.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
My love,
your head is bobbing.
Oh.
Is there something
on your mind?
Weird.
Uh, no.
Nothing at all.
Definitely nothing to hide.
That's for sure.
You can go harder.
I like the pain.
Oh.
We might need a safe word.
- Hey.
What are you doing out here?
I worked late, so...
I got tired on my way home,
pulled over.
My house isn't
on your way home.
You got me.
I just came by to make sure
you're doing OK.
And you slept out here?
I mean, how did you even
use the bathroom?
Wait.
Is this about the alien stuff
that you said the other night?
Aliens?
That's crazy.
No, I just--
checking up on you.
If that keeps aliens away,
then great.
I was not abducted by aliens,
so you need to go home
before Kate comes out
and starts asking questions.
- Fine.
Hey, would you toss
my water bottle for me?
Did you piss in it?
You know I did.
Pretty full.
Smells like pee-pee.
Would you throw it out,
yes or no?
- No.
- Give it a toss.
It's full of urine.
Really?
It's just pee.
Love ya.
Huh. Lovely.
There you are.
Tell me you did not spend
another night
guarding Ben and Kate's house.
Yeah, but he caught me,
so can't do that again.
Tonight I'll have to bring
binoculars
and park up the street,
watch from there.
What's the plan here?
Let's say you witness
an abduction.
How exactly are you
gonna stop it?
Baseball bat.
I've seen pictures of Greys
on the internet.
Their long necks,
their heads are
just right in my strike zone.
Not to complain,
but would it kill Jay
to wash a dish once in a while?
That sounds like complaining.
I know.
She's your daughter,
and that actually
explains why she doesn't clean.
But her stuff is everywhere.
Pullout couch, always open.
Oh, my raspberry yogurt's
gone again.
Big surprise.
- You finished that yesterday.
- Yeah.
Because I knew if I didn't,
Jay would eat it.
Fine.
I'll buy you more yogurt
and clean.
Happy?
No.
Jay should be doing that.
Look, things are really good
between Jay and I right now,
and I don't want
to rock the boat.
Besides, we have
bigger things to worry about,
like how to keep Harry
from leaving with Heather.
Jay seems like
the least of our--
Sup, fam?
You're out of milk, FYI.
Jay's the least of our--
you were saying?
Leave me alone.
Nothing like
a good gill excavation
to make you feel new again.
What can I do to thank you?
You don't need to thank me.
I don't deserve it.
You deserve everything.
That is why
I will finish this bomb,
so that we can leave
and we can never look back.
I cannot wait to see
your planet.
Will your friends accept
that you are dating
an un-winged alien?
Let's not talk
about the future.
Let's just--let's just talk
about the present
because it's so special.
You know, I think that's
why they call it the present,
'cause it's a present.
That reminds me,
I wrote you a--a new poem.
You did?
I love your poems.
But don't read it to me.
Stop right there
and do not read it,
because I'm gonna
take this out,
and if I don't come right back,
that's just because
I ran out to get cigarettes.
But you do not even smoke.
I love that you try new things.
This must be
what true love is like.
When your lover leaves,
you feel like
you will never see them again.
And the sound of her tires
peeling out of my driveway,
I can tell she is in a hurry
to come back to me.
Here you go, Debra.
Morning, Sheriff.
Hey, Deputy.
Hey, do you ever
get the feeling like--
like you're being followed?
Right now comes to mind.
Last night,
I felt someone following me.
So this morning,
I changed up my route,
but I think that son of a bitch
Joseph is still on my tail.
You know what this means,
don't you?
We're on the right track
with our investigation.
Our investigation? No.
I told you, when I get
involved, people get hurt.
I'm done.
What?
I thought you just needed time.
I don't need time.
I need distance.
Taking time helps you see
things more clearly, Deputy.
Hey, you know, Cletus peed
in my bed once, right?
Now, I got mad,
but did I get rid of him?
No.
I took some time to reflect
and find the right move.
So then I went and peed
in his little doggy bed,
and I said to him,
"Now, how do you like it now?"
That's how he learns.
They pee on you,
you pee on them.
I'm not gonna
rub his nose in it.
That'd just be cruel.
Not more cruel than me
listening to this story.
Hey.
Uh, I need to talk to you guys
about something.
I have had some complaints
regarding
the Sheriff's Department.
I told you
it was a terrible idea
to put up that suggestion box.
Yes, I got that from the note
you put in the suggestion box
telling me to take down
the suggestion box.
It seems certain constituents
aren't happy
about their taxpayer dollars
being wasted investigating
alien-related matters.
Taxpayers shouldn't
have a say
in how their tax dollars
are spent.
That's anarchy.
Well, some people
call it democracy.
Exactly.
This is a free country.
People can look for aliens
if they want,
or search the forest
for fairies,
even if they only find
a small frog
living in an old shotgun shell.
You said certain people
are lodging complaints.
I want to know who.
I am not at liberty to say.
Hi, Sheriff.
Nana.
Thank you, Mayor,
for our little talk.
Oh, come on, Liv.
How do you expect people
to take you seriously
with that crease
in your britches?
Ugh.
She's right.
I do have a crease.
How did she see that?
Sheriff, I'd like to see you
in my office.
Mm.
All right, Sheriff,
have a... seat.
I asked to see you
in my office.
No, you said
you'd like to see me
in your office.
And I don't blame you.
Hell, I'm a statue
of masculinity.
If I was in your office,
you'd probably walk in
every morning and say, "Damn,
now, that's what I want to be."
If you were a statue
in my office,
I'd hang my jacket on you.
I'd want you to,
because I'd be made
out of metal, and I'd be cold.
See?
Even as a statue man,
I still get what I want.
OK, here's the thing.
You and Liv have been
seen around town
snooping in plain clothes,
investigating something.
Not to mention, you know,
how you practically begged me
for a new deputy,
but now he's gone,
and you haven't even
replaced him?
What is going on?
Why are you being so secretive?
Why are you being
so inquisitive?
Because I have
a right to know.
This is my town.
- Oh, really?
You obviously don't know
how towns work.
You ever see a Western?
It's the sheriff that says,
"You're in my town now,"
not the mayor.
Do you drive a car
that has "mayor" written on it?
Yes, I do.
- You do?
- Yes.
Sometimes when it's dirty,
Max writes "mayor"
in the window,
and that's mayor,
as in "may your...
"town, if it is in trouble,
I will be the one to fix it."
You may have the word "sheriff"
on your car door,
but the name "Hawthorne"
is printed
on the soul of this town.
Right.
Like that poison creek.
Forget about the creek.
That's being renamed.
I don't know why
you're being like this.
You know, we used to be
like partners.
We were never partners.
We operate under
a split form of government,
like Madagascar or East Timor,
with two leaders
sharing separate powers, OK?
Now, if you don't mind,
I got work to do.
Humans thrive on forming
connections to each other.
But when that connection
is broken,
it makes them feel untethered.
They do not like that.
That is how I am
starting to feel.
Heather has been gone
for two hours,
and all I can think of is,
what if she is hurt?
What if she has been plucked
and stuffed into a pillow
or cozy lightweight jacket?
Hello.
Oh.
Thank you.
"Harry, if you're
reading this,
"then you've met
my friend Arlo.
I'm leaving the planet
without you."
No.
"Don't look for me.
"And please give Arlo
some cereal,
if you don't mind."
This cannot be.
♪ One is
the loneliest number ♪
"How do I know
this is really you?
Also, I am out of cereal."
♪ Two can be as bad as one
♪ It's the loneliest number
OK, there you go.
♪ Since the number one
Oh, so fast.
You're back.
♪ No is the saddest
experience ♪
"Yes, it's really me.
"Who else would send
a note by pigeon?
PS, Arlo also enjoys
a nice cracker."
"Why?
"What has happened?
"Also, Arlo would not
eat my crackers.
They were the pepper kind."
♪ One is
the loneliest number ♪
♪ One is the loneliest
number ♪
♪ Number that you'll ever do
Heather.
We can't keep doing
the notes.
It's not fair to Arlo.
He's freakin' exhausted.
My love, you came back.
No, Harry, it's over.
What?
But why?
Because I don't love you.
I never did.
No.
I don't believe you. Ah! Ow.
Why? Ow.
I think my heart is stopping.
It's not.
Hearts are the only thing
in the universe
that work even after
they break.
It's the thing that sucks
about hearts.
How do you know that?
Is it because your heart
is breaking too?
No.
My heart's fine.
Feels great.
Well, you cannot
take our love.
It is not just yours.
It is also mine.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
No, wait, I--
I have a--a poem to read you.
You have to listen.
It is titled
"Forever Together."
"Boy, I just
can't stop smiling."
- No, I can't do this.
I cannot do this.
Good--
Good what?
"Good"?
"Goodness, I love you."
"Good thing I was joking."
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Huh?
"Bye."
"Goodbye."
Why?
Got you, son of a bitch.
Wait, you're not Joseph.
I--I'm Troy.
Troy?
Whoa.
Are you Lena's son?
I was just curious.
I wanted to see the guy
my mom was dating.
Come on, son.
You can't be
following people around
in the dark, all right?
It's dangerous.
And you can relax.
We're not dating.
We're just colleagues.
She doesn't talk about
her other colleagues
the way she talks about you.
She talks about me?
I overheard her
telling my Aunt Naya
you don't like her
paying for stuff?
I don't get it.
What's wrong with her paying?
Look, I appreciate
that you're here
to protect your mom, all right?
But this is grown man stuff.
You wouldn't understand.
It's complicated.
No, it's not.
From now on,
you stay away from her.
OK, well, she's already
staying away from me.
Why wouldn't she?
You made her cry.
What kind of a man are you?
Harry?
I got a text saying
you want to die,
followed by an emoji
of a skull,
then a noose, then a gun.
Yeah.
And then a knife and a casket.
Then for some reason, a church?
That was a mistake.
It was supposed to be a sword.
What's going on?
Heather left me.
Yes.
Yes, she did.
And that is awful.
She's gone.
It's over.
Now my life is over.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Harry.
Do not lie.
You're happy.
The red-haired one
is trying not to smile.
It seems like you know
my name by now.
OK.
Look, we did try
to break you guys up,
but it didn't work.
- Right.
So maybe it's just you.
Is that helping?
I...
You're wrong.
Heather loved me.
I loved her.
I don't know what happened.
Sometimes there is
no explanation.
Oh.
Hey.
You just need to get your mind
off her, you know.
Stay busy.
Focus on
your little project here.
Huh, what is it?
Some kind of alien bird feeder?
- It's a bomb.
- A bomb, you say.
What's that now?
I built it
for the general to use
on the Greys
after I left with Heather.
OK.
Well, saving the Earth,
that's something to live for.
I don't care about the Earth.
This place sucks.
I hate it here!
Uh!
Hey, Greys!
Come and take this Earth!
I don't want it!
You can have it!
Hey, take this stupid plant!
I don't want it!
You can have it!
Take this stupid chair!
Huh?
I don't care anymore!
- OK.
- Take me!
I want to die!
OK, will you come back
in here, please?
Maybe you'll feel better
if you eat something.
We got you a pizza.
I do not care
about your pizza.
I hate the Earth,
and I hate you.
Whoa!
That is not how I taught you
to behave.
Asta worked hard to pay
for that pizza, young man.
You will get your butt
out here and eat it.
I don't care, and I hate you!
I hate you more!
You know,
for the first time in my life,
I feel like I have
what it takes to be a mother.
I finally met Lena's son.
He's been tailing me.
He wanted to see
who his mom was dating.
Wanna talk about it?
Nah.
There's nothing to talk about.
She said we're colleagues,
but then I find out
she's been crying
over the breakup.
Seems like you want
to talk about it.
No, no.
This is our quiet time.
Quiet time.
You know,
maybe it's my destiny,
you know, to be alone.
OK.
Let's talk about it.
Her kid's right.
What kind of man
has somebody special
then just--
just pushes her away?
The kind of man
that lost his mom
when he was young
and raised by his father.
You got attached to these
notions of masculinity.
So take it easy on yourself.
It's not your fault.
Now can we fish?
You're the one
who wanted to talk.
He was serious about leaving.
This thing has
all the instructions
on what to do with this bomb.
Well, anything productive
is on hold for a bit.
He just asked
if men can be nuns.
Probably for the best.
I don't know if I want him
handling a bomb right now.
I am so tired of playing
parent to this alien child.
It's enough to do it at home.
Yeah.
What?
Nothing.
You're just not really
doing it at home.
I told you, Jay and I
are in a good place.
I don't want to ruin that.
- Right.
You're afraid to piss off
the teenager who lives with us
and eats my yogurt,
so now I have no yogurt.
I am not afraid.
Yes, you are.
You're afraid
you're gonna lose her.
And you're aiding
and abetting her.
Aiding and abetting?
What, is yogurt-eating
a felony now?
No, it's just,
you're trying to be
her friend instead of just
being a responsible adult.
If I'm so irresponsible,
why do you come running to me
every time you're in trouble?
Because you let me,
which might be
how this whole problem got
started, if I'm being honest.
Oh, oh, OK.
So I've ruined you
because I'm there for you
when you need me?
No, you're there for me
when it suits you,
when it makes you feel
better about yourself,
like Harry said.
Thank you.
Tell me one time
that I was not there for you.
Oh, I don't know,
maybe when you drove me insane
by keeping
a life-altering secret from me
for a year and a half?
Oh, really? This again?
What was I supposed to do,
tell you the new doctor
is an alien?
Yes!
I'm supposed to be
your best friend,
but you couldn't
share that with me.
Why?
I'm not getting into this.
Well, we're in it.
Let's just drop it, please.
I don't want to drop it.
I want to know why.
Because you're
a loose cannon,
and I didn't know
if I could trust you.
Is that what you want to hear?
You are so impulsive,
I just knew that
you would tell someone.
That's bullshit.
You didn't want to tell me
because Harry
dropping down to Earth
was a godsend for you.
Just you.
Secret little baby
you found on your doorstep,
another one for your
menagerie of the needy.
You told Ben that
he was getting abducted
when I told you not to.
You did it anyway
because you don't listen
because you make everything
about yourself.
I do not.
How do I make everything
about myself?
Tell me. I want to know.
A lot of "I's" and "me's"
in that denial.
I told Ben
because real friends
don't keep huge secrets
from each other.
You told Ben
because you feel guilty,
and so you made everything
about you.
OK, fine. Fine.
I make everything about me.
But you make everything
about you
by saying it's not about you
because you're a martyr.
I'd rather be a martyr
than a loose cannon.
Well, that is exactly
what a martyr would say.
- Loose cannon.
- Martyr.
Pretend I'm not here.
Why are you here?
I came to see
how you're doing.
Were you getting dressed?
Undressed?
Or is this just how it is now?
Would you ask a woman that?
Your friend Asta
contacted me.
Said you're a mess
and can't work.
Now, I don't know
the first thing
about how to console
a lovesick alien,
but I heard about
your chicken girlfriend
or whatever she was.
So...
What the hell is that?
The guy said
her name is Patricia.
I thought maybe
she could help you
get over your girlfriend.
No judgment.
Everyone has their thing.
I am offended that you think
you can replace
the love of my life
with just some random bird.
No offense.
This has nothing
to do with you.
You're very attractive.
Do whatever you need.
Just finish that bomb.
And don't fall in love.
She's a rental.
Don't worry, we don't
have to do anything.
We can just talk.
And even though I've never
had a UFO encounter myself,
I'm here
to support my daughter,
because I love her.
I love you too, Mom.
Oh, baby.
OK.
Thank you for sharing, Dorothy.
So this is where
all the crazies meet.
I expected there'd be
more padding on the walls.
- Hi.
- You came.
Yeah.
I was in the neighborhood,
so I figured I might as well.
You're new.
You want to tell us
a little about yourself
and why you're here?
Oh, me? No.
Um, I'm--I'm not here
to participate.
I'm--I'm just here to watch.
We don't get
a lot of watchers here.
Well, I--I haven't
experienced anything.
I mean, I--
I've been seeing this owl
outside my window.
But it's not a big deal.
I mean,
this is Colorado, right?
There are owls.
14 varieties, actually.
I--I looked it up online.
So, you know, no, I--
I think I'm good.
Except, um, I'm not--
I'm not good.
I'm...
I used to like where I live.
But now--I mean,
I love our--our home, but...
But I don't feel safe there.
I mean, I--I even--
I even tried to convince
my husband to sell our house.
But I--I think
it's bigger than that.
Like, I think
I'm not safe anywhere.
And I just feel like
I'm going crazy.
Oh, am I allowed to use
that word in here?
You're not crazy.
I've had a similar experience.
At first, the owls
didn't seem odd,
but then it just
kept happening.
I even put our house up
on the market.
And then one day,
I'm in the shower,
and I find this tiny bump
behind my knee
that I'd never noticed.
So I did some research,
and I realized
it's maybe a chip
they implanted in me,
and that people
all over the world
have been having
similar experiences.
Are you OK?
I don't know.
Does he have any idea
you were taking his DNA?
No.
I feel terrible, though.
I love him.
Oh, that's sweet.
You love your niece?
My knees?
You're gonna break my knees?
Niece.
Your niece, your sister's kid.
- OK.
Well, you could have
just said my sister.
I love her too.
Oh, snap.
Niece and knees,
very different.
How so?
Niece is a little girl
or a city in France.
I don't break knees.
I'm here on the scene,
watching Asta's boyfriend
and Harry's girlfriend
having a rendezvous.
Both of them sound like
my sister's girl child.
You have a niece
called knees?
Yeah. She's my niece.
How are we losing
to you people?
Shift reports
for you to sign.
Everything OK, Deputy?
You got your sad face on.
Really?
I have a sad face?
I'll give you a tip.
Here, put this pencil
in your mouth.
Sideways.
There you go.
You feel your smile muscles
stretching out?
See, when you're sad,
you fool your body
into thinking you're happy,
then you feel happy.
How long does it take?
Uh, seven minutes.
Of course, I'm a pro,
so I did it in three
using that very same pencil.
So tell me, Deputy,
what's got you down?
I went to one
of my meetings today.
And this woman, Linda,
brought her mom.
She just came
to support her daughter.
I never had
that kind of support,
and I probably never will.
Mm.
You know what?
Take a seat, Deputy.
I--I want to tell you
a story about this guy.
- Is this guy you?
Uh, doesn't matter.
Anyway, there's
this really handsome guy
that smells really good, right?
And he lost his mother
in his teens.
Now, his father--
- Lewis?
Can I finish telling you
the story about this guy?
- Yeah.
- OK, so his--his father,
he may have pushed
his notions of masculinity
on this guy
a little too hard, right?
And maybe if this guy would
have confronted his issues
earlier in life,
he wouldn't have
let his ego get the best of him
and pushed away
a perfectly good woman.
Is the woman Lena Torres?
Let's call her Meena Flores.
OK, look, my point is,
we're shaped by the people
who raise us.
And the people around you
weren't very supportive.
In fact, they actively
held you down.
Now, you are
the strongest person I know,
except when you're around
your Grandma Patty.
You need to stand up to her.
I can't.
She's mean and gives
deceptively powerful noogies.
Well, what if I told you
I knew a guy who'd go with you
and give you all the support
you've never had?
Is this guy you?
Ha!
You finally figured it out.
♪ Took a vacay from
♪ The ways
that you're used to ♪
♪ It's a new day
to find a way to a new you ♪
♪ I'm really not sure what
you thought I signed up for ♪
♪ Skip the encore,
I've had enough ♪
♪ I don't need more
I'll give you
a lesson sometime.
Been trying
to get ahold of you,
but I see you were busy.
Dude, the snow was awesome.
You should have come with us.
Yeah, it must be nice
to take off work on a whim.
So impulsive, you know?
OK.
So what, you have a problem
with me snowboarding now?
Nope.
Where is Harry?
I don't know.
Last time I saw him,
I was with you.
Well, I went to the cabin,
and he isn't there.
All I found was a giant bird
who isn't Heather.
He definitely has a type.
OK.
Why are you looking for him?
Judy saw Joseph
talking to Heather.
What? Where?
I'm here on the scene,
watching--
Ignore the--
she had a filter on.
I can't hear
what they're saying.
What the hell?
Is the bird a spy
for the Greys?
We have to find Harry
and tell him.
I know where he goes
when he gets depressed.
Thanks for taking us
up the mountain, Steve.
Yeah, no problem.
I've gotta do a flyby
of the south peak anyway.
I think you and I have
to come clear it on Saturday.
Cool.
Avalanche control
is important, right?
Hey, are you concerned at all
that I'm some kind
of loose cannon
and that I'll go
up there with you
and just push you
off the mountain?
Um, no.
Ah.
So you don't think
I'm a loose cannon.
So you trust me.
Interesting.
Steve, don't you think
it's weird for someone
to give you shit for spending
time with your daughter?
I don't have a daughter.
Yeah, but don't you think,
after everything
you've been through,
you've earned the right
to hang out with her?
You know,
be a little more carefree.
Hey, Steve, do you think
painting the bathroom
a combination
of mauve and vomit
makes bath time enjoyable?
Steve, would you buy
a tiny coffee table
that's so small, it won't even
hold coffee table books?
We don't have
coffee table books.
Because the coffee table
is too small.
Oh, my God. I--
I can't knock.
I'm too nervous.
This always happens
when I come here.
It's OK.
You just got yourself
a little case of "shy-knuckle."
I'll be with you the whole way.
Go ahead, make a fist.
Ow.
I think they're
bleeding a little.
Liv. Sheriff.
What's going on?
I wanted to talk to you
about something.
And you couldn't just
send me an email?
Why did I bother
learning the internet
if you're just going
to show up in person?
All right, come in.
Wipe your feet.
It's not a flophouse.
Well, what is it?
You know
all that stuff you say
about my hair and my face
and pretty much
everything about me?
Yeah.
It--it feels kind of mean.
But it's probably
not your fault,
because I know your generation
has had it hard
with wars and everything,
and um,
I know you were born
in Great-grandpop's hay wagon.
Oh, you wanted to apologize.
OK, fine.
I forgive you.
Is that it?
- Yep.
Uh, wasn't there, uh--
wasn't there something else?
Ay-yi-yi.
OK, I admit,
I stole your
deviled egg recipe, Nana,
but it's only because
I admire your cooking,
and I admired you.
I wanted to be like you,
but then you trash-talked me
to the whole family.
And now you've said
all those awful things
about me in the town paper.
Why would you do that?
I just told the truth.
I always do.
Oh, really?
Well, I can do
some truth-telling too.
Oh.
Grandmothers are
supposed to be nice
and smell like cookies,
but you are cruel and vicious,
and you smell like vinegar.
And not that sweet balsamic
stuff that you dip bread in,
but that British
french fry vinegar.
OK, you're getting
a little off track.
Little girls
are supposed to be happy
to see their grandmas,
but I always dreaded it,
because you made me feel
small and worthless,
and I still feel that way,
but I'm not going to anymore,
because you're the one
who's small,
and you're the one
who's worthless.
Dial it back a little bit.
You are an old, angry
piece of---- -------,
and you can take that------ deviled egg----
and whip up some------ recipe
and-------
jam up it up your----------!
OK, all right.
That's enough.
No, no, no.
I'm just getting started.
She's faking it.
Gary said she'll be OK.
It's just a minor heart attack.
I mean, she looked pale
when we showed up,
so she was probably already
pre-heart attacking.
Thanks.
Also, I told Garrett
she's delusional.
So no one will believe
her side of the story.
I like living
in a small town.
Yeah.
You get your recipes?
Thanks for picking the lock.
Let's go.
We were never here.
No way.
♪ If I could be,
baby, where you are ♪
♪ Then I would know
♪ Baby, what you know
Told you he'd be here.
♪ Just to be, baby,
where you are ♪
What are you two doing here?
Heather's working
with Joseph.
It is bad enough
that she is gone.
Now you are spreading lies
about the woman
that I used to love
and now wish was dead.
It's not a lie, Harry.
Judy saw Heather
give Joseph a trash bag.
Do you know why?
Was it a blue trash bag?
Yeah.
She cleaned my gills
and put the gunk in there.
Do you know why she'd want
to give that stuff to Joseph?
My DNA.
They want to clone me.
They have my alien ball.
They're trying
to manipulate it.
But I gave it to Robert,
the alien tracker's son.
If the Greys kidnapped him,
then they have the ball.
You have reception here?
How?
It's very easy.
You just go into settings.
It will prompt you.
"Would you like to harness
the mountain
"to use as your own
personal cell tower
because you're
a brilliant alien?"
And you just push "yes."
So funny.
Hello, son.
It is Harry, your new father.
Uh, not the dead one.
Uh, how are you?
Are you still on Earth?
Yeah.
I'm at the malt shop
with the fellas.
The Greys have the ball.
What are they
gonna do with it?
Our technology is all
hydrogen-based.
It helps us manipulate water.
But if the Greys can do it,
they can speed up
their plans for the cavern
at Yellowstone.
Wait, so they could destroy
the Earth any time now?
Worse.
The love of my life
did not just leave me.
She betrayed me.
Love is like a lifeline
that tethers an astronaut
to his ship.
If that line is cut,
you are lost.
That is how I feel,
cut off from the only love
I will ever know.
When the connection to what
we believe and trust is lost,
it is like the air
that we breathe is gone.
D'Arcy,
let's just talk, please?
♪ Images of you
♪ It's constant torture
♪ But I don't know
what else to do ♪
And then being connected
becomes a matter of survival.
♪ Only those big black
buzzards ask how I've been ♪
♪ Ain't you proud
♪ Oh, oh, hey
♪ She was a blue avian
♪ Now we are apart
♪ I hope that
there's a giant wolf ♪
♪ That will rip out
her dead heart ♪
♪ There is no love
♪ I can't believe it
♪ But it's true
♪ It's true
♪ And I'm angry
♪ I'm angry, I'm angry,
I'm angry, I'm angry ♪
What the hell?
♪ Made for you
and looks so fine ♪
So what brings you
to this neck of the woods?
♪ That's the way
it will always be ♪
I'm here to kill my father.
♪ Oh, remember
every day you find ♪
♪ You got a little trouble
on your mind ♪
♪ You'll find me near
'cause I'll always be ♪
♪ Just for you
and you for me ♪